<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="quarter_prefix_array">
        <item>In the name of Allah, the Entirely Merciful, the Especially Merciful.</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah is not timid to present an example - that of a mosquito&#8230;</item>
        <item>Do you order righteousness of the people and forget yourselves while&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [recall] when Moses prayed for water for his people, so We said,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Do you covet [the hope, O believers], that they would believe for you&#8230;</item>
        <item>And Moses had certainly brought you clear proofs. Then you took the&#8230;</item>
        <item>We do not abrogate a verse or cause it to be forgotten except that We&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [mention, O Muhammad], when Abraham was tried by his Lord with&#8230;</item>
        <item>The foolish among the people will say, \"What has turned them away&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, as-Safa and al-Marwah are among the symbols of Allah . So&#8230;</item>
        <item>Righteousness is not that you turn your faces toward the east or the&#8230;</item>
        <item>They ask you, [O Muhammad], about the new moons. Say, \"They are&#8230;</item>
        <item>And remember Allah during [specific] numbered days. Then whoever&#8230;</item>
        <item>They ask you about wine and gambling. Say, \"In them is great sin and&#8230;</item>
        <item>Mothers may breastfeed their children two complete years for whoever&#8230;</item>
        <item>Have you not considered those who left their homes in many thousands,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Those messengers - some of them We caused to exceed others. Among&#8230;</item>
        <item>Kind speech and forgiveness are better than charity followed by&#8230;</item>
        <item>Not upon you, [O Muhammad], is [responsibility for] their guidance,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And if you are on a journey and cannot find a scribe, then a security&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"Shall I inform you of [something] better than that? For those&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah chose Adam and Noah and the family of Abraham and the&#8230;</item>
        <item>But when Jesus felt [persistence in] disbelief from them, he said,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And among the People of the Scripture is he who, if you entrust him&#8230;</item>
        <item>All food was lawful to the Children of Israel except what Israel had&#8230;</item>
        <item>They are not [all] the same; among the People of the Scripture is a&#8230;</item>
        <item>And hasten to forgiveness from your Lord and a garden as wide as the&#8230;</item>
        <item>[Remember] when you [fled and] climbed [the mountain] without looking&#8230;</item>
        <item>They receive good tidings of favor from Allah and bounty and [of the&#8230;</item>
        <item>You will surely be tested in your possessions and in yourselves. And&#8230;</item>
        <item>O mankind, fear your Lord, who created you from one soul and created&#8230;</item>
        <item>And for you is half of what your wives leave if they have no child.&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [also prohibited to you are all] married women except those your&#8230;</item>
        <item>Worship Allah and associate nothing with Him, and to parents do good,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah commands you to render trusts to whom they are due and&#8230;</item>
        <item>So let those fight in the cause of Allah who sell the life of this&#8230;</item>
        <item>What is [the matter] with you [that you are] two groups concerning&#8230;</item>
        <item>And whoever emigrates for the cause of Allah will find on the earth&#8230;</item>
        <item>No good is there in much of their private conversation, except for&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, be persistently standing firm in justice,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Allah does not like the public mention of evil except by one who has&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, We have revealed to you, [O Muhammad], as We revealed to Noah&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, fulfill [all] contracts. Lawful for you are&#8230;</item>
        <item>And Allah had already taken a covenant from the Children of Israel,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And recite to them the story of Adam\'s two sons, in truth, when they&#8230;</item>
        <item>O Messenger, let them not grieve you who hasten into disbelief of&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, do not take the Jews and the Christians as&#8230;</item>
        <item>O Messenger, announce that which has been revealed to you from your&#8230;</item>
        <item>You will surely find the most intense of the people in animosity&#8230;</item>
        <item>Allah has made the Ka\'bah, the Sacred House, standing for the people&#8230;</item>
        <item>[Be warned of] the Day when Allah will assemble the messengers and&#8230;</item>
        <item>And to Him belongs that which reposes by night and by day, and He is&#8230;</item>
        <item>Only those who hear will respond. But the dead - Allah will resurrect&#8230;</item>
        <item>And with Him are the keys of the unseen; none knows them except Him.&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [mention, O Muhammad], when Abraham said to his father Azar, \"Do&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah is the cleaver of grain and date seeds. He brings the&#8230;</item>
        <item>And even if We had sent down to them the angels [with the message]&#8230;</item>
        <item>For them will be the Home of Peace with their Lord. And He will be&#8230;</item>
        <item>And He it is who causes gardens to grow, [both] trellised and&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"Come, I will recite what your Lord has prohibited to you. [He&#8230;</item>
        <item>Alif, Lam, Meem, Sad.</item>
        <item>O children of Adam, take your adornment at every masjid, and eat and&#8230;</item>
        <item>And when their eyes are turned toward the companions of the Fire,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And to the \'Aad [We sent] their brother Hud. He said, \"O my people,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Said the eminent ones who were arrogant among his people, \"We will&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We inspired to Moses, \"Throw your staff,\" and at once it&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We made an appointment with Moses for thirty nights and perfected&#8230;</item>
        <item>And decree for us in this world [that which is] good and [also] in&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [mention] when We raised the mountain above them as if it was a&#8230;</item>
        <item>It is He who created you from one soul and created from it its mate&#8230;</item>
        <item>They ask you, [O Muhammad], about the bounties [of war]. Say, \"The&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, the worst of living creatures in the sight of Allah are the&#8230;</item>
        <item>And know that anything you obtain of war booty -  then indeed, for&#8230;</item>
        <item>And if they incline to peace, then incline to it [also] and rely upon&#8230;</item>
        <item>[This is a declaration of] disassociation, from Allah and His&#8230;</item>
        <item>Have you made the providing of water for the pilgrim and the&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, indeed many of the scholars and the monks&#8230;</item>
        <item>And if they had intended to go forth, they would have prepared for it&#8230;</item>
        <item>Zakah expenditures are only for the poor and for the needy and for&#8230;</item>
        <item>And among them are those who made a covenant with Allah, [saying],&#8230;</item>
        <item>The cause [for blame] is only upon those who ask permission of you&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah has purchased from the believers their lives and their&#8230;</item>
        <item>And it is not for the believers to go forth [to battle] all at once.&#8230;</item>
        <item>And if Allah was to hasten for the people the evil [they invoke] as&#8230;</item>
        <item>For them who have done good is the best [reward] and extra. No&#8230;</item>
        <item>And they ask information of you, [O Muhammad], \"Is it true?\" Say,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And recite to them the news of Noah, when he said to his people, \"O&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We took the Children of Israel across the sea, and Pharaoh and&#8230;</item>
        <item>And there is no creature on earth but that upon Allah is its&#8230;</item>
        <item>The example of the two parties is like the blind and deaf, and the&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [Noah] said, \"Embark therein; in the name of Allah is its course&#8230;</item>
        <item>And to Thamud [We sent] their brother Salih. He said, \"O my people,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And to Madyan [We sent] their brother Shu\'ayb. He said, \"O my&#8230;</item>
        <item>And as for those who were [destined to be] prosperous, they will be&#8230;</item>
        <item>Certainly were there in Joseph and his brothers signs for those who&#8230;</item>
        <item>And women in the city said, \"The wife of al-\'Azeez is seeking to&#8230;</item>
        <item>And I do not acquit myself. Indeed, the soul is a persistent enjoiner&#8230;</item>
        <item>They said, \"If he steals -  a brother of his has stolen before.\"&#8230;</item>
        <item>My Lord, You have given me [something] of sovereignty and taught me&#8230;</item>
        <item>And if you are astonished, [O Muhammad] -  then astonishing is their&#8230;</item>
        <item>Then is he who knows that what has been revealed to you from your&#8230;</item>
        <item>The example of Paradise, which the righteous have been promised, is&#8230;</item>
        <item>Their messengers said, \"Can there be doubt about Allah, Creator of&#8230;</item>
        <item>Have you not considered those who exchanged the favor of Allah for&#8230;</item>
        <item>Alif, Lam, Ra. These are the verses of the Book and a clear Qur\'an.</item>
        <item>And that it is My punishment which is the painful punishment.</item>
        <item>The command of Allah is coming, so be not impatient for it. Exalted&#8230;</item>
        <item>And it will be said to those who feared Allah, \"What did your Lord&#8230;</item>
        <item>And Allah has said, \"Do not take for yourselves two deities. He is&#8230;</item>
        <item>Allah presents an example: a slave [who is] owned and unable to do a&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah orders justice and good conduct and giving to relatives&#8230;</item>
        <item>On the Day when every soul will come disputing for itself, and every&#8230;</item>
        <item>Exalted is He who took His Servant by night from al-Masjid al-Haram&#8230;</item>
        <item>And your Lord has decreed that you not worship except Him, and to&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"Be you stones or iron</item>
        <item>And We have certainly honored the children of Adam and carried them&#8230;</item>
        <item>Do they not see that Allah, who created the heavens and earth, is&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [had you been present], you would see the sun when it rose,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And present to them an example of two men: We granted to one of them&#8230;</item>
        <item>I did not make them witness to the creation of the heavens and the&#8230;</item>
        <item>[Al-Khidh r] said, \"Did I not tell you that with me you would never&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We will leave them that day surging over each other, and [then]&#8230;</item>
        <item>So she conceived him, and she withdrew with him to a remote place.</item>
        <item>But there came after them successors who neglected prayer and pursued&#8230;</item>
        <item>Ta, Ha.</item>
        <item>From the earth We created you, and into it We will return you, and&#8230;</item>
        <item>[ Allah ] said, \"And what made you hasten from your people, O&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [all] faces will be humbled before the Ever-Living, the Sustainer&#8230;</item>
        <item>[The time of] their account has approached for the people, while they&#8230;</item>
        <item>And whoever of them should say, \"Indeed, I am a god besides Him\"- &#8230;</item>
        <item>And We had certainly given Abraham his sound judgement before, and We&#8230;</item>
        <item>And [mention] Job, when he called to his Lord, \"Indeed, adversity&#8230;</item>
        <item>O mankind, fear your Lord. Indeed, the convulsion of the [final] Hour&#8230;</item>
        <item>These are two adversaries who have disputed over their Lord. But&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah defends those who have believed. Indeed, Allah does not&#8230;</item>
        <item>That [is so]. And whoever responds [to injustice] with the equivalent&#8230;</item>
        <item>Certainly will the believers have succeeded:</item>
        <item>How far, how far, is that which you are promised.</item>
        <item>And even if We gave them mercy and removed what was upon them of&#8230;</item>
        <item>[This is] a surah which We have sent down and made [that within it]&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, do not follow the footsteps of Satan. And&#8230;</item>
        <item>Allah is the Light of the heavens and the earth. The example of His&#8230;</item>
        <item>And they swear by Allah their strongest oaths that if you ordered&#8230;</item>
        <item>Blessed is He who sent down the Criterion upon His Servant that he&#8230;</item>
        <item>And those who do not expect the meeting with Us say, \"Why were not&#8230;</item>
        <item>And it is He who has released [simultaneously] the two seas, one&#8230;</item>
        <item>Ta, Seen, Meem.</item>
        <item>And We inspired to Moses, \"Travel by night with My servants; indeed,&#8230;</item>
        <item>They said, \"Should we believe you while you are followed by the&#8230;</item>
        <item>Give full measure and do not be of those who cause loss.</item>
        <item>Ta, Seen.  These are the verses of the Qur\'an and a clear Book</item>
        <item>[Solomon] said, \"We will see whether you were truthful or were of&#8230;</item>
        <item>But the answer of his people was not except that they said, \"Expel&#8230;</item>
        <item>And when the word befalls them, We will bring forth for them a&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We had prevented from him [all] wet nurses before, so she said,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And when Moses had completed the term and was traveling with his&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We have [repeatedly] conveyed to them the Qur\'an that they might&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Qarun was from the people of Moses, but he tyrannized them.&#8230;</item>
        <item>Alif, Lam, Meem</item>
        <item>And Lot believed him. [Abraham] said, \"Indeed, I will emigrate to&#8230;</item>
        <item>And do not argue with the People of the Scripture except in a way&#8230;</item>
        <item>Alif, Lam, Meem.</item>
        <item>[Adhere to it], turning in repentance to Him, and fear Him and&#8230;</item>
        <item>Allah is the one who created you from weakness, then made after&#8230;</item>
        <item>And whoever submits his face to Allah while he is a doer of good - &#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"The angel of death will take you who has been entrusted with&#8230;</item>
        <item>O Prophet, fear Allah and do not obey the disbelievers and the&#8230;</item>
        <item>Already Allah knows the hinderers among you and those [hypocrites]&#8230;</item>
        <item>And whoever of you devoutly obeys Allah and His Messenger and does&#8230;</item>
        <item>You, [O Muhammad], may put aside whom you will of them or take to&#8230;</item>
        <item>If the hypocrites and those in whose hearts is disease and those who&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We certainly gave David from Us bounty. [We said], \"O mountains,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"Who provides for you from the heavens and the earth?\" Say, \"&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"I only advise you of one [thing] -  that you stand for Allah,&#8230;</item>
        <item>O mankind, you are those in need of Allah, while Allah is the Free of&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, Allah holds the heavens and the earth, lest they cease. And&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We did not send down upon his people after him any soldiers from&#8230;</item>
        <item>Did I not enjoin upon you, O children of Adam, that you not worship&#8230;</item>
        <item>[The angels will be ordered], \"Gather those who committed wrong,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And indeed, among his kind was Abraham,</item>
        <item>But We threw him onto the open shore while he was ill.</item>
        <item>And has there come to you the news of the adversaries, when they&#8230;</item>
        <item>And with them will be women limiting [their] glances and of equal age.</item>
        <item>And when adversity touches man, he calls upon his Lord, turning to&#8230;</item>
        <item>So who is more unjust than one who lies about Allah and denies the&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"O My servants who have transgressed against themselves [by&#8230;</item>
        <item>Ha, Meem.</item>
        <item>Have they not traveled through the land and observed how was the end&#8230;</item>
        <item>And O my people, how is it that I invite you to salvation while you&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, [O Muhammad], \"Indeed, I have been forbidden to worship those&#8230;</item>
        <item>Say, \"Do you indeed disbelieve in He who created the earth in two&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We appointed for them companions who made attractive to them what&#8230;</item>
        <item>To him [alone] is attributed knowledge of the Hour. And fruits emerge&#8230;</item>
        <item>He has ordained for you of religion what He enjoined upon Noah and&#8230;</item>
        <item>And if Allah had extended [excessively] provision for His servants,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And it is not for any human being that Allah should speak to him&#8230;</item>
        <item>[Each warner] said, \"Even if I brought you better guidance than that&#8230;</item>
        <item>And when the son of Mary was presented as an example, immediately&#8230;</item>
        <item>And We had already tried before them the people of Pharaoh, and there&#8230;</item>
        <item>It is Allah who subjected to you the sea so that ships may sail upon&#8230;</item>
        <item>Ha, Meem.</item>
        <item>And mention, [O Muhammad], the brother of \'Aad, when he warned his&#8230;</item>
        <item>Have they not traveled through the land and seen how was the end of&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, obey Allah and obey the Messenger and do not&#8230;</item>
        <item>Certainly was Allah pleased with the believers when they pledged&#8230;</item>
        <item>O you who have believed, do not put [yourselves] before Allah and His&#8230;</item>
        <item>The bedouins say, \"We have believed.\" Say, \"You have not [yet]&#8230;</item>
        <item>His [devil] companion will say, \"Our Lord, I did not make him&#8230;</item>
        <item>[Abraham] said, \"Then what is your business [here], O messengers?\"</item>
        <item>There will circulate among them [servant] boys [especially] for them,&#8230;</item>
        <item>And how many angels there are in the heavens whose intercession will&#8230;</item>
        <item>The people of Noah denied before them, and they denied Our servant&#8230;</item>
        <item>The Most Merciful</item>
        <item>When the Occurrence occurs,</item>
        <item>Then I swear by the setting of the stars,</item>
        <item>Has the time not come for those who have believed that their hearts&#8230;</item>
        <item>Certainly has Allah heard the speech of the one who argues with you,&#8230;</item>
        <item>Have you not considered those who make allies of a people with whom&#8230;</item>
        <item>Have you not considered those who practice hypocrisy, saying to their&#8230;</item>
        <item>Perhaps Allah will put, between you and those to whom you have been&#8230;</item>
        <item>Whatever is in the heavens and whatever is on the earth is exalting&#8230;</item>
        <item>And when you see them, their forms please you, and if they speak, you&#8230;</item>
        <item>O Prophet, when you [Muslims] divorce women, divorce them for [the&#8230;</item>
        <item>O Prophet, why do you prohibit [yourself from] what Allah has made&#8230;</item>
        <item>Blessed is He in whose hand is dominion, and He is over all things&#8230;</item>
        <item>Nun. By the pen and what they inscribe,</item>
        <item>The Inevitable Reality -</item>
        <item>Indeed, mankind was created anxious:</item>
        <item>Say, [O Muhammad], \"It has been revealed to me that a group of the&#8230;</item>
        <item>Indeed, your Lord knows, [O Muhammad], that you stand [in prayer]&#8230;</item>
        <item>I swear by the Day of Resurrection</item>
        <item>There will circulate among them young boys made eternal.  When you&#8230;</item>
        <item>About what are they asking one another?</item>
        <item>The Prophet frowned and turned away</item>
        <item>When the sky breaks apart</item>
        <item>When the sky has split [open]</item>
        <item>Exalt the name of your Lord, the Most High,</item>
        <item>I swear by this city, Makkah -</item>
        <item>Did We not expand for you, [O Muhammad], your breast?</item>
        <item>But does he not know that when the contents of the graves are&#8230;</item>
    </string-array>
    
</resources>